Wolfram Rong
I am a multidisciplinary web dev. and experience designer. I specialize in front-end dev and I love to create new and uncommon experiences.

Relevent Skills
Markup: HTML5, HAML, Handlebars, Markdown, HTML Email
Stylesheets: CSS3, SASS, LESS, PostCSS
Scripting: JS(ES6), JQuery, AJAX & JSON, PHP
Frameworks
CSS: Bootstrap, Foundation, SemanticUI, MDL
JS/PHP: Laravel, Lumen, MeteorJS
CMS: Wordpress
Query: MySQL, SQLite, MongoDB
Design: Photoshop, Illustrator, Sketch
Prototyping: Axure, InVision

Experience
Freelancer (9/13 - Present)
Worked on a variety of projects editing designs and turning mockups into working webpages, HTML emails, or WP themes. 
Created and/or edited custom backends and CMSs

DESIGNATION Labs (05/15 - 05/16)
Developer & Mentor
Developed and maintained marketing and public-facing websites using HTML, CSS, JS, and the LAMP stack.
Fixed and optimized existing codebases to be more functional and performant.
Sourced, edited, and published design blogs.
Ran UX and Dev. workshops for students.
Assisted with complex code modifications for student portfolios.

Georgia Tech (08/14 - 01/15)
PR Assistant — Contract
Designed outreach, networking, and advertising materials using Photoshop and Illustrator.
Created and maintained an internal assets database.

Monmouth University (5/14 - 8/14)
Research Assistant — Contract
Managed a project updating a suite of software tools for university faculty.
Designed and coded the asyncronous front-end components using Bootstrap.
Led small group of 3 other interns.

Other Interests
I’m currently exploring AR/VR technologies using Unity and the HTC Vive. I’m also a mentor for two FIRST Robotics teams in Pilsen and New City in Chicago.